http://www.ipipi.com/DisplayContent.do?page=privacyPolicy

Privacy Policy
ipipi.com ("The Service") is a service provided
by Upside Wireless Inc. ("Upside"). We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to
learn more about our privacy policy.
Coverage
This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") covers how our service treats
personal information that our service
collects and receives, including information
related to your past use of this service and
your communications with our service and
Upside.
This Privacy Policy applies to activities of Upside and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively "Upside", "we" or "us").
Definition
Personal information is information about
you that is personally identifiable like your
name, address, email address, or phone number.
It also includes information you store in your
account about your contacts (for example their
names and contact information) and transactional
information that is generated in the process of
your using our service (messages you send and receive including
their
content, phone numbers and/or email addresses).
Information Collection and Use
We collect personal information when you register with our service and when you use our service.
When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, zip code and personal interests. Once you register with our service and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
We collect information about your login and messaging transactions with us.
We store information about your contacts - people you interracted with using our service.
You can view the entire content of what we store about you from a GDRP report available in your account. To view it, please login to your account and click Account->GDRP Report.
We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your
IP Address, cookie information, and the page you request.
We use information to fulfill your requests for our services, to improve our services, contact you, to conduct internal research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal purposes.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you, nor contacts you enter in your address
book,
with other people or non-affiliated companies except:
when
we have your explicit permission,
when we are requested to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise
our legal rights or defend against legal
claims.
to prevent misuse. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action
regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of
use, or as otherwise required by law.
Cookies
We may set and access cookies on your computer for the purpose of allowing you easier access to your account.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
You can edit your personal account information, including your preferences at any time.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our services, such as service announcements and administrative messages.
You can delete your account on Account->GDRP page in your account.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come
into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that protect
your personal information.
Your Account Information is password-protected.
Your account password is encrypted.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy that materially change how we treat your personal information, we will endeavor to provide you with reasonable notice of such changes, such as via prominent notice in the Quora Platform or to your email address of record, and where required by law, we will obtain your consent or give you the opportunity to opt out of such changes.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please
contact us
Coverage / Login / Privacy / Terms / Help
© 2001-2017 Upside Wireless Inc. All rights reserved
